[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which film did Salma Hayek play the role of a famous woman-artist?", "correct_answer": "Frida", "incorrect_answers": ["In the Time of the Butterflies", "After the Sunset", "Traffic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was the movie Over Her Dead Body filmed?", "correct_answer": "Los Angeles", "incorrect_answers": ["New York", "Sydney", "San Francisco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these inventions hit the market in 1982?", "correct_answer": "The compact disk", "incorrect_answers": ["The flying auto", "The  TV remote control", "The wireless bra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where and when was the movie Scarface set?", "correct_answer": "Florida in 1980", "incorrect_answers": ["Florida 1983", "Cuba 1981", "Cuba in 1984"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Back to the Future, what did Goldie Wilson do in 1955, before becoming mayor?", "correct_answer": "Worked in the diner", "incorrect_answers": ["Played in Marvin Berrys rock and roll group", "He was a drifter", "Pumped gas at the filling station"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the Emperor who introduced the first cycle of Chinese zodiac in 2637 BC?", "correct_answer": "Huang Ti", "incorrect_answers": ["Ming Shu", "Tsian Tza", "Fei Lin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of animated character, named Darlin, did Whoopi Goldberg voice in the 2006 animated movie Everyones Hero?", "correct_answer": "Baseball bat", "incorrect_answers": ["Golf cart", "Computer mouse", "Cat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average temperature on the Martian surface?", "correct_answer": "-23 degrees Celsius", "incorrect_answers": ["23 degrees Celsius", "0 degree Celsius", "100 degrees Celsius"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What American actress voiced Princess Fiona in the 2001 animated comedy movie Shrek?", "correct_answer": "Cameron Diaz", "incorrect_answers": ["Angelina Jolie", "Renee Zellweger", "Julia Roberts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the movie Sleepless in Seattle released?", "correct_answer": "1993", "incorrect_answers": ["2004", "1972", "1985"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1987 thriller Fatal Attraction, what is the occupation of Michael Douglas character Dan Gallagher?", "correct_answer": "Attorney", "incorrect_answers": ["Doctor", "Book publisher", "Ad executive"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Sin City, Marv eats Kevin.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]